Alchemy is a science where one understands the structure of matter, breaks it down, then rebuilds it.
錬金術は物質を理解分解再構築する科学なり
However, it is not an all-powerful technique,
as one cannot create something out of nothing.
されど万能の技にはあらず
無から有を生ずることあたわず
If one wishes to gain something,
one must present something of equal value.
何かを得ようと欲すれば
必ず同等の代価を支払うものなり
This is the concept of equivalent exchange, the fundamental basis of alchemy.
これすなわち錬金術の基本　等価交換なり
However, there is a taboo in alchemy. Human transmutation.
錬金術師に禁忌あり
そは人体錬成なり
One must not commit this act.
これ何人も犯すことなかれ
I've still got a lot of years ahead of me
この想いを　消してしまうには
Kono omoi wo keshiteshimau niwa
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
Mada jinsei nagai desho?
To just erase these feelings?
まだ人生長いでしょ？
I want to go back and finish
やり残してるコト
Yarinokoshiteru koto
The things that I've yet to finish.
やり直してみたいから
Yarinaoshite mitai kara
I was supposed to be chasing after my ongoing dream,
夢のつづき　追いかけていたはずなのに
Yume no tsuzuki oikaketeita hazu nanoni
Yet I faltered over others while walking this thin, winding path.
曲がりくねった　細い道　人につまずく
Magarikunetta hosoi michi hito ni tsumazuku
It's not that I want to return to those days.
あの頃みたいにって　戻りたい訳じゃないの
Ano koro mitainitte modoritai wake ja nai no
I'm searching for the sky I lost.
無くしてきた空を　探してる
Nakushitekita sora wo sagashiteru
Don't make that sad face, as if you've fallen victim.
わかってくれますように
Wakatte kuremasu youni
As if you want people to pity you.
犠牲になったような　悲しい顔はやめてよ
Gisei ni natta youna kanashii kao wa yameteyo
Tears aren't the end of your sins.
罪の最後は涙じゃないよ
Tsumi no saigo wa namida ja nai yo
You have to bear them painfully, forever.
ずっと苦しく背負ってくんだ
Zutto kurushiku seottekunda
Who are you waiting for in the maze of emotions,
出口見えない感情迷路に
Deguchi mienai kanjoumeiro ni
Where you can't even see the exit?
誰を待ってるの？
Dare wo matteruno?
I want to blurt it out more justly,
白いノートに綴ったように
Shiroi nooto ni tsuzutta youni
Just like how I wrote it in my white notebook.
もっと素直に吐き出したいよ
Motto sunao ni hakidashitai yo
What do you want to run from?
何から　逃れたいんだ
Nani kara nogaretainda
That thing called "reality"?
…現実ってやつ？
Genjitsu tte yatsu?
I just want to scream out,
叶えるために　生きてるんだって
Kanaeru tame ni ikiterundatte
"I'm only living to fulfill my wish." Can you hear me?
叫びたくなるよ　聞こえていますか？
Sakebitaku naru yo kikoeteimasuka?
I can't take the safe way out of everything.
無難になんて　やってられないから
Bunan ni nante yatterarenaikara
I don't even have a place to return to.
…帰る場所も無いの
Kaeru basho mo nai no
I'm always thankful for everyone's kindness,
優しさには　いつも感謝してる
Yasashisa ni wa itsumo kansha shiteru
That's why I want to become stronger. (I'm on the way)
だから強くなりたい(I'm on the the
(I'm on the way)
Dakara tsuyoku naritai (I'm on the way)
This is reminding me of the old days.
懐かしくなる
Natsukashiku naru
This pain is all right with me.
こんな痛みも歓迎じゃん
Konna itami mo kangei jan
In the city of Lior, a High Priest of Leto deceived people through the use of the Philosopher's Stone and alchemy.
リオールの街では
レト教の教主が賢者の石と錬金術を使い
人々を欺いていた
Ed and Al, who ventured into the church, stopped the High Priest's plot.
教会へ乗り込んだエドたちは
教主の悪だくみを食い止める
However, the Philosopher's Stone was a fake.
しかし　賢者の石は偽物だった
"Get up and take a step. Walk forward."
「立って歩け　前へ進め」
Ed's words pierced Rose's chest, who had lost all hope.
希望を失ったロゼの胸に　エドの言葉が刺さる
それはエドが自分たちへ向けた言葉でもあった
But, those words were also meant for themselves, as well.
You're Basque Gran, the "Iron Blood Alchemist", aren't you?
鉄血の錬金術師　バスク·グランだな
Who are you?
何者だ
Alchemists who go against God's path...
神の道に背きし錬金術師
...shall perish!
滅ぶべし
So you're the killer who only goes after State Alchemists.
国家錬金術師ばかりつけ狙う殺人鬼とは貴様のことか
But!
だが
You picked... the wrong opponent!
相手が悪かったな
You're fast! But...
速い　だが
Well, then...
ならば
How foolish.
たわいもない
W-What?!
なっなんだと
Perish.
滅びよ
Another State Alchemist?
また国家錬金術師が
Looks like quite a mess.
相当な手だれですな
You have to be careful, too, Major.
少佐も気をつけろよ
You may be his next target.
次に狙われるのは　あんたかもしれんぞ
Yes, sir...
はい
Führer President!
大総統閣下
Why are you here, sir?
どうしてこちらへ
I heard the news.
知らせを聞いてな
Lt. Colonel Hughes, are you in charge of dealing with this matter?
ヒューズ中佐　この事件の担当かね
Yes, sir!
は
必要な人員があれば要請したまえ
If there are people whom you require assistance from, request them immediately.
反逆者には　鉄槌を下さねばならん
We must bring the iron hammer down on the traitors.
は
Yes, sir!
Second Lieutenant Breda.
ブレダ少尉
All right...
うす
Seriously... The Colonel must have been procrastinating again.
ったく
また大佐　仕事ため込んでたんすねぇ
Hey, Havoc, do half of these for me.
おいハボック　半分手伝ってくれよ
I've got my hands full over here, too.
こっちもいっぱいいっぱいだって
Umm, who is this again?
えっと　誰だこれ
That's Lieutenant Yoki.
ヨキ中尉ですね
He's a little rascal who was lining his pockets with the authority he was given at the coal mines of Youswell.
ユースウェル炭坑の利権で
私腹を肥やしてた小悪党ですよ
He's currently on the run after having
his actions exposed by the Elric Brothers.
エルリック兄弟に悪事を暴かれて
現在逃亡中です
Sergeant Fuery, how is the radio?
フュリー曹長　無線機はどう
The receiver is broken.
受信機がダメですね
We'll need to replace some parts...
部品を換えないと
Edward-kun! Alphonse-kun!
エドワード君アルフォンス君
Welcome back, you two.
おかえりなさい二人とも
The Colonel has been waiting for you.
大佐がお待ちかねよ
The matter in Lior is settled all thanks to you.
リオールの件　君たちのお陰だ
I'd like to express my gratitude.
感謝を述べておこう
It wasn't for you or anything.
別に　あんたのためじゃねぇよ
で　賢者の石は今回も不発か
And, was the search for
the Philosopher's Stone a failure again?
The stone was a fake.
石は偽物だった
But the power was unbelievable.
けど　力だけはとんでもなかったよ
He transmuted a huge chimera, too.
バカでかい合成獣を錬成してたしな
I wonder how you could use the stone to make something like that?
石をどう使えばあんなことできるんだろう
I'm not really familiar with the field of
Biological Alchemy, so I wouldn't know, but...
生体錬成の分野には詳しくないから
よく分からないけど
Yeah, I'm a little curious.
でも　ちょっと興味あるな
If we put our effort into researching it,
we may find something useful in getting our bodies back.
ちゃんと調べたら
体を取り戻すのに役立つことがあるかもしれない
Yeah.
うん
Then, how about seeking help from a specialist?
なら専門家の助けを借りてはどうだ
Huh?
The Sewing-Life Alchemist, Shou Tucker.
綴命の錬金術師　ショウ·タッカー
He is a scholar in chimera Transmutation.
合成獣錬成の研究者だ
会わせてやろう
I'll introduce you to him.
You're going to go out of your way to do that?
大佐がわざわざ
I-It's a trap! There's definitely more than meets the eye!
う裏だ　絶対裏がある
Don't look at me with those suspicious eyes!
疑わしい目で見るんじゃない
We're even after that case in Lior!
これでリオールの件はチャラだ
It just feels disgusting to know that I owe you.
君に借りをつくるのは気色が悪いからな
Tucker became a State Alchemist two years ago after transmuting a chimera that understood human language.
タッカーは２年前
人語を解する合成獣の錬成に成功して
国家錬金術師の資格を取った
"Understood human language"?
人語を解するって　しゃべるの合成獣が
It could speak?! The chimera?!
Yeah. Apparently, it did.
ああ　しゃべったそうだ
Just one sentence...
ただひと言
"I want to die."
「死にたい」と
It never ate afterwards and died.
その後　エサも食べずに死んだそうだ
What a huge house.
でっけぇ家ん
B-Brother!
にっ兄さん
Wow, we've got a lot of visitors!
お客さんいっぱい
Nina, we have to keep the dog tied down.
ニーナ　犬はつないでおかなくっちゃ
いや　申し訳ない
I'm terribly sorry.
This house has been in a mess ever since my wife left.
妻に逃げられてから　うちの中もこの有様で
Well, pleasure to meet you, Edward.
改めて　はじめましてエドワード君
I'm Shou Tucker, the Sewing-Life Alchemist.
綴命の錬金術師　ショウ·タッカーです
He is interested in the transmutation of living organisms.
彼は生体の錬成に興味があってね
He said he would love to have
the honor of seeing your work.
ぜひあなたの研究を拝見したいと
Sure, that's fine with me.
ええ　かまいませんよ
One thing, though...
ただ
If you'd like for me to show you my hand,
人の手の内を見たいというなら
I'm going to need to see yours, too.
君の手の内も明かしてもらわないとね
Isn't that what being an alchemist is about?
それが錬金術師というものだろ
Why are you interested in the transmutation of the living organisms, exactly?
なぜ生体の錬成に興味を
Oh, well... he's...
あっいや　彼は
Colonel.
大佐
Transmutation of your mother?!
母親の錬成を　１１歳の子供が
As an eleven year old child?!
Ah, I see. So that's why you're called "The Fullmetal Alchemist"...
そうか　それで「鋼の錬金術師」と
You've experienced a tough past, haven't you...
つらい経験をしたんだね
I'm not sure whether I could be of any help at all,
役に立てるかどうかは分かりませんが
but please take a look at my laboratory.
私の研究室を見てもらいましょう
Wow...
Ah, this is a little embarrassing.
いや　お恥ずかしい
People call me the "authority" on chimeras, but in reality, it's not really going very well.
巷では　合成獣の権威なんていわれてるけど
実際のところ　そんなにうまくはいってないんだ
Wow, this is awesome!
おお　すっげぇ
That's the reference room. Feel free to take a look around.
資料室だ　自由に見ていいよ
All right. Then I'll start with this shelf.
よし　オレはこっちの棚から
Then I'll start with that one over there.
じゃあ　僕はあっちから
I'll be returning to work.
私は仕事に戻る
I'll send someone to pick them up in the evening.
夕方　迎えの者をよこそう
Wow, he's really into it.
すごい集中力ですね
He can't even hear what's going on around him.
もう周りの声が聞こえていない
I guess geniuses really do exist.
いるんですね　天才ってやつは
Up high! Up high!
高いぞ　高いぞ
Al, what the heck are you doing?!
アル　何やってんだよ
Nina seemed like she wanted someone to play with her.
ニーナ遊んでほしそうだったから
Hey, what the heck do you think we're here for-
お前な　何しにここへ
Alexander wants someone to play with, too, he says.
アレキサンダーも遊んでほしいって
You've got some guts.
いい度胸だ
It's said that even when hunting rabbits, lions put forth their fullest effort.
獅子はうさぎを狩るのにも全力を尽くすという
I, Edward Elric, shall deal with you with all of my physical and spiritual might!!!
このエドワード·エルリックが
全身全霊で相手してくれるわ
You damn dog!!!
犬畜生めぇ
Yo Boss, I've come to pick you up.
よう大将
迎えに来たぞ
What are you doing?
何やってんだ
Eh, just taking a break from research...
いや　資料検索の息抜きというか
Did you manage to get good data?
いい資料は見つかったかい
You're welcome to visit tomorrow, too.
また明日おいで
You'll come visit again?
また来てくれるの
Let's play tomorrow, all right, Nina?
明日遊ぼうね　ニーナ
Okay!
うん
Oh right, Mr. Tucker, I've got a message for you from the Colonel.
ああ　タッカーさん
大佐から伝言が
He told me to tell you, "It's almost the day of the assessment. Don't forget."
「もうすぐ査定の日です　お忘れなく」だそうです
Yes, understood.
ええ　分かっております
Well, then.
じゃあ
Daddy.
お父さん
What's an "assessment"?
「さてい」ってなぁに
Well...
A State Alchemist has to report the results of his experiments once a year.
国家錬金術師は年に一度
研究の成果を報告しなくちゃいけないんだ
Daddy couldn't get a good evaluation last year.
お父さん　去年はあまりよい評価をもらえなくてね
If Daddy messes up this year,
Daddy won't be a State Alchemist anymore.
今年失敗すると
国家錬金術師じゃなくなってしまうんだよ
What?!
ええっ　お父さんなら大丈夫だよ
You'll be fine, Daddy!
You're always studying so much!
いつもいっぱい勉強してるもん
You're right. I've got to do my best.
そうだね　頑張らないと
This... is my last chance...
もう　あとがないんだ
えっ　お母さんが２年前に
Huh, your mother left home two years ago?
実家に帰っちゃったってお父さんが言ってた
Daddy told me that she went back to her parents' home.
そっか
Oh... it must be kind of lonely for you,
being alone with your daddy in a big house like this.
こんな広い家にお父さんと二人じゃさみしいね
ううん　平気
Nope, I'm fine.
お父さん優しいし　アレキサンダーもいるから
Daddy's really nice, and I've got Alexander with me, too.
でも　お父さん最近研究室ばっかりだから
But... Daddy's always at his lab these days, so..
ちょっとさみしいな
I guess I'm kind of lonely...
Ugh, my shoulders have gotten a little stiff.
ああ　肩凝ったなぁ
Why don't you exercise a bit, Brother?
少し運動すれば　兄さん
That sounds kind of nice.
それもいいなぁ
おら　犬
Hey, dog!
オレの運動につきあえ
Accompany me on my exercises!
You, too, Nina.
さあ　ニーナも
ああちょっちょっちょっちょっちょっちょっちょっ
Wait up!
待って
そらっ
Watch this!
Hey, hey, hey!
それそれそれ
Wait, you!
待たんかいこら
Wait!
待て
You can do it, Alexander!
アレキサンダー頑張って
"It's almost the day of the assessment. Don't forget."
もうすぐ査定の日です　お忘れなく
But... why does he only target State Alchemists?
しかし　国家錬金術師ばかり狙うってのはどういうわけだ
軍が標的なら　無差別に軍人を襲えばいい
If the army is his target, he can just attack soldiers indiscriminately.
特殊能力を持つ錬金術師は楽に殺せる相手じゃない
Since Alchemists possess special abilities, they're not easy to kill.
And one with a state qualification should be much tougher.
まして　国家資格を持つ者となれば
その資格が原因なのでは
Perhaps it's the qualification that's the reason?
Hm?
莫大な報酬とさまざまな特権
An immense reward and various privileges.
Many are envious of them.
これを羨む者は多いでしょう
しかも　錬金術師よ
Also...
"Alchemists, work for the good of the public."
大衆のためにあれ
Alchemists, who are supposed to be searching for the truth,
真理の探究者だったはずの錬金術師が
国家資格を得た途端　軍の人間兵器に変わる
turn into the army's human weapons
as soon as they earn their state qualifications.
かのイシュヴァールの内戦以来
And also, after that civil war in Ishbal,
there are many who hold a grudge against us.
恨みを持つ者はいくらでもおりますからな
報告します　昨日午後９時３０分ごろ
Reporting.
Yesterday, around 9:30PM, many station employees witnessed a man with a large scar on his face at Central City Station.
セントラルシティ駅構内において
顔に大きな傷のある男を
複数の駅員が目撃したとのことです
Station?!
駅　野郎逃げたか
Did he run away?!
国家資格を取る前の暮らしは　ひどいもんだったよ
Our lives before I got my state qualification were terrible.
貧しくてね
We were so poor.
そんな生活に耐えきれず　妻は出ていってしまった
My wife couldn't stand living in conditions like that, and she left our home.
I need to pass the assessment, no matter what...
なんとしても査定を通らないと
あのころには　二度と戻りたくないから
I don't ever want to return to those days.
It's okay, Daddy!
大丈夫よお父さん
If they tell you "No", Alexander and I will go and scold the higher-ups!
ダメだって言われたら
私とアレキサンダーが偉い人に怒ってあげる
ニーナは強いな
Nina sure is strong.
ニーナ　明日はお父さんと一緒に遊ぼうか
Nina... what do you say we play together tomorrow?
本当
Really?!
Yeah.
ああ
Yay!
やった
アレキサンダー　お父さんが遊んでくれるって
Alexander, Daddy said he'd play with us tomorrow!
こんにちは　タッカーさん
Good morning, Mr. Tucker!
今日もよろしくお願いします
We're going to be using your place again today!
Huh?
あれ
タッカーさん
Mr. Tucker?
おい　ニーナ
Hey! Nina?
Mr. Tucker?
タッカーさん
なんだ　いるじゃないか
Oh, so you are here.
やあ
Hey...
出来たよ　完成品だ
It's complete. The finished product.
人語を理解する　合成獣だ
A chimera that understands human language.
見てくれ
Watch.
This person is Edward. Got it?
いいかい　この人はエドワード
エドワード
Ed...ward...
That's right! I'm so proud of you!
そう　よくできたね
This is amazing... it really did talk.
すげぇ　ほんとにしゃべってる
あぁ　これで国家資格を失わずに済むよ
Now I won't have to lose my state qualification.
エドワード
Ed...ward...
おにいちゃん
O...nii...chan...
タッカーさん
Mr. Tucker...
国家資格取ったのいつだっけ
When did you get your state qualification again?
It was two years ago, I believe.
ええっと　２年前だね
奥さんがいなくなったのは
And when did your wife leave you?
２年前だね
Two years ago.
もう一つ質問いいかな
Can I ask you another question?
ニーナとアレキサンダー　どこ行った
Nina and Alexander...
Where are they?!
君のような勘のいいガキは嫌いだよ
I don't like sharp brats like you.
兄さん
Brother!
ああそういうことだ　やりやがったな
Yeah, that's how it is!
You've done it, haven't you?!
２年前はてめぇの妻を
It was your wife two years ago,
and this time, you used your daughter and your dog to transmute a chimera!
そして今度は娘と犬を使って合成獣を錬成しやがった
動物実験にも限界があるからな
Since there are limits to animal experimentation, after all!
It must be a breeze if you use a human!!!
楽だろうさ　人間使えばなぁ
W-What's there to get angry about?
な　何を怒ることがある
The mankind's advances are the product of many experiments on humans, aren't they?
人類の進歩は　無数の人体実験のたまものだろう
If you're a scientist, too, then you should-
君も科学者なら
ふざけんな
Don't screw around with me!!!
Do you really think something like this will be forgiven?!
こんなことが許されると思ってんのか
Something like this... toying with human life?!
こんな　人の命を弄ぶようなことが
人の命　はははっ
Human life?
Ah, human life, you say?
そう　人の命ねぇ
Fullmetal Alchemist!
鋼の錬金術師
Your limbs and your younger brother.
君のその手足と弟
Aren't those the results of what you're saying right now? Toying with human life?
それも　君が言う人の命をもてあそんだ結果だろう
NO!!!
違う
同じだよ　君も私も
We're the same!
You and I!
No, we're not!!!
違う
Yes, we are!
違わないさ
目の前に可能性があったから試した
There was a possibility in front of us, so we tested it out.
Even though we knew it was taboo!
それが禁忌であると知っていても
You're wrong!!!
違う
オレは
I!
錬金術師は
Alchemists!
こんなこと
Don't!
オレは　オレは
I... I!!!
Brother!
兄さん
If you go any further, he'll die!
それ以上やったら死んじゃう
お父さん　痛い
Da...ddy...
Does it hurt?
お父さん　痛い
ごめんね　僕たちの力では君を元に戻してあげられない
I'm sorry.
We can't change you back to normal with our powers.
ごめんね　ごめんね
I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
Let's... play.
遊ぼうよ　遊ぼうよ
Let's play...
間に合ったんだ　これでまた国家錬金術師に
I made it in time.
With this, I can continue being a State Alchemist...
何が国家錬金術師だ　何が
State Alchemist, my ass...
Stop kidding yourself...
Let's... play.
あそぼうよ
くそぉ
DAMMIT!!!
If something such as an act of the Devil exists in this world,
悪魔の所業というものがこの世にあるなら
this case is just that.
今回の件は　まさにそれですね
悪魔か
The Devil, huh...
But if it is an order, State Alchemists must make
their move, without hesitation, to take human lives.
だが　国家錬金術師は
命あらば人の命を奪うことも辞さず　行動せねばならん
人の命をどうこうする点で
If it's about handling human lives,
there really isn't much difference between where we stand and what Mr. Tucker did.
タッカー氏の行為と我々の立場に大きな差はない
そしてそれを承知のうえで　この道を選んだ
You were aware of that, and yet you chose this path.
そうだろ　鋼の
Am I right, Fullmetal?
今後も今回のような事件に出くわすことはあるだろう
I'm sure you'll run into incidents like this in the future again.
There may be times when you have to soil your hands.
君自身が手を汚すこともあるかもしれん
その度に　そうやって立ち止まるのか
Are you going to come to a stop like that every time it happens?
Whether they call me a dog of the military, or curse me as a devil,
軍の狗と呼ばれようが
悪魔と罵られようが
Al and I will get back our bodies.
オレはアルと二人　元の体に戻ってやる
だけどな
But...
We're neither devils,
オレたちは悪魔でも　ましてや神でもない
nor gods at that!
We're humans...
人間なんだ
人間なんだよ
We're just humans!!!
たった一人の女の子さえ助けてやれない
Puny, powerless humans...
...who can't even save one little girl.
ちっぽけな人間だ
なんで誰も分かってくれないんだろうな
I wonder why no one understands us...
ニーナ
...Nina...
ショウ·タッカーだな
You're Shou Tucker, aren't you?
誰だ
Who are you?
Looks like... you're not from the military!
軍の者ではないな
どうやって入ってきた
How did you get in?!
There should have been military policemen stationed out front!
表に憲兵がいたはずだ
Alchemists, who go against God's path...
神の道に背きし錬金術師
滅ぶべし
...shall perish!
お父さん
Da...ddy...
お父さん　お父さん
Daddy...
哀れな　この姿になってしまっては元に戻る方法はない
How miserable...
But now that you are in a state like that,
there is no way to return you to normal.
せめて安らかに逝くがよい
At the very least, leave this world in peace.
神よ
God,
two souls have just returned to your side.
今二つの魂があなたの許へ還りました
その広き懐に彼らを迎え入れ
Please usher them into your broad bosom,
and grant rest and salvation to their miserable souls.
哀れな魂に安息と救いを与えたまえ
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
Do you remember it from that day?
ねえ　君は覚えていますか
Nee kimi wa oboeteimasuka
We made a promise and a vow while the early summer wind circled us.
約束　契り　初夏の風が包む
Yakusoku chigiri shoka no kaze ga tsutsumu
And we clung close together.
二人　寄り添った
Futari yorisotta
Your forced smile
無理な笑顔の裏
Muri na egao no ura
Holds elongated shadows.
伸びた影をかくまう
Nobita kage wo kakumau
I pretend not to notice and continue on.
だから　気づかぬふり　再生を選ぶ
Dakara kizukanu furi saisei wo erabu
All the while waiting for you to deliver some news at the table.
テーブルの上の　震えない知らせ　待ち続けて
Teeburu no ue no furuenai shirase machitsuzukete
Empty nights, mornings that will never arrive,
空白の夜も　来るはずのない朝も
Kuuhaku no yoru mo kuru hazu no nai asa mo
I could see them from a mile away.
全部わかってたんだ
Zenbu wakattetanda
Say, the sky we saw that day, the scarlet sky.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
Ano hi mita sora akaneiro no sora wo
I'm sure you'll remember it one day.
ねえ　 いつか思い出すでしょう
Nee itsuka omoidasu deshou
While holding the promise we couldn't keep,
果たせなかった　約束を抱いて
Hatasenakatta yakusoku wo idaite
We take our first steps down our own paths.
二人　歩き出す
Futari arukidasu
ニーナの死に打ちひしがれるエドとアルを
日本语字幕录入：FAYFAY
The rain pours down in East City.
謎の男スカーが襲う
Still grief-stricken over Nina's death,
漫游字幕组
http://popgo.net/bbs
Ed and Al are attacked by the mysterious man, Scar.
次回　鋼の錬金術師
FULLMETAL ALCHEMIST
In a life-or-death crisis, Ed makes a desperate decision.
第五話　悲しみの雨
Next time, Fullmetal Alchemist:
Episode 5, Rain of Sorrows.
一緒に行こう　エウレカ
俺は君が大好きだ
Will he be ready to accept the decision brought on by desperation?
レントン　レントン　レントン